Finding Aid for the Alfred Leonard and Joseph Leonard Collection PASC-M.0180
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Clippings, Advertisements, Reviews, Series V.
  - Pertaining to Babin-Vronsky, Subseries 4.
    - Boros, Ethel. [Article on Babin appointment as director of Cleveland Institute of Music]. newspaper clipping; 1 p. (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Article in Cleveland Plain Dealer, Saturday, August 19, 1961.
    - Swanton, Marilyn. [Article on Vronsky]. newspaper clipping; 1 p. (Box 20, Folder 9)
      Article on p. 22 of Cleveland Plain Dealer, August 31, 1961.
  - Other, Subseries 5.
    - [Clipping with death notice of Josef Rainz]. newspaper clipping; 1 leaf`. (Box 18, Folder 27)
      Clipping from unidentified German newspaper. Article circled in blue pencil.
    - [Review of Grauden Ensemble debut]. clipping; 1 p. (Box 18, Folder 38)
      Clipping from unknown source.
    - [Clipping from unidentified German newspaper]. 1 leaf. (Box 18, Folder 39)
      Does not appear to contain any references to Levi-Leonard family members.
    - [Newspaper clipping from Mannheimer Tageblatt]. newspaper clipping; 1 leaf. (Box 19, Folder 17)
      Pp. 1-2 of Mannheimer Tageblatt from Thursday, December 18, 1930; no discernable reference to Levi family.
    - [Clipping from Kunst-Wissen-Leben]. newspaper clipping; 1 leaf. (Box 19, Folder 18)
      Mannheim-based Kunst-Wissen-Leben, February 18, 1930. No discernable reference to Levi-Leonard family.
    - [German newspaper fragments]. newspaper clippings; 4 leaves. (Box 19, Folder 19)
      4 fragments from unidentfied German language newspapers.
    - Adoration of the Magi by Fra FIlippo Lippi. poster; 18x18. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - [1945-1946 Behymer concert series]. 1 leaf. (Box 21, Folder 2)
      Clipping torn from unidentified source; pencil markings on Behymer subscription series information.
- Books and Monographs, Series VI.
  - By P. Alfred Leonard, Subseries 1.
    - Leonard, Alfred. Masters Immortal. xerox; 31 p. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Contains biographies of Western Classical composers. Published by Adohr Milk Farms, which also sponsored the Golden Hour radio program. Monograph provided free by request during 1940 concert series. See 18/5 for original.
    - Leonard, Alfred. A Music Lover's Notebook. original; xerox; 47 p. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      2 items: original monograph and xerox copy. Published by Adohr Milk Farms, which also sponsored the Adhor Golden Hour radio program. Monograph provided free of charge to listeners during 1941 concert series.
    - Leonard, Alfred. Music in Your Home. 23 p. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Published by Adohr Milk Farms in conjunction with "The Golden Hour" radio show, 1939.
    - Leonard, Alfred. Masters Immortal. 32 p. (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Contains biographies of Western Classical composers. Published by Adohr Milk Farms, which also sponsored the Golden Hour radio program. Monograph provided free by request during 1940 concert series. See 16/1 for xerox copy. Original location in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook. See 8/5.
  - Other books and monographs, Subseries 2.
    - Weingartner, Felix. On Conducting. 56 p. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Translated by Ernest Newman, published by E. F. Kalmus Orchestra Scores, Inc.
    - Rodriguez, Jose ed. Music and Dance in California. 468 p. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Collection of essays edited by Jose Rodriguez, compiled by William J. Perlman. Published by Bureau of Musical Research, Hollywood 1940. Contains articles by Ernst Toch "Toward New Sonorities" and Alfred Leonard "The Phonograph's Role and Importance".
    - Galleria degli Uffizi - Firenze Sculptures. book cover only; 2 leaves. (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Articles, Lectures, Sermons, Other Writings, Series VII.
  - By P. Alfred Leonard, Subseries 1.
    - Leonard, Alfred. Suicide, Reasons Unknown by Germanicus. typewritten ms; xerox; 7 p. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Full title: Suicide, Reasons Unknown - A Frequent News Caption in New Germany by Germanicus. Original and xerox copy.
    - Leonard, Alfred. How to Plan the Home Entertainment Center. 1 p. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Clipping from Arts and Architecture, February 1953.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Address in Honor of Ernst Toch's 75th Birthday]. xerox of ms; 8 p. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Address given December 1962 at Austrian Government party held in New York.
    - [Leonard, Alfred]. Praktische Leute. typewritten ms; 1 p. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Possibly typed by Leonard; original location in folder marked "Alfred Leonard writings".
    - [Leonard, Alfred]. Tragikomisches aus Hitler Germany. typewritten ms; 3 p. (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Original location in folder marked "Alfred Leonard writings".
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Commentary on contemporary developments in Germany]. mimeograph of ms; 11 p; letter; 3 leaves. (Box 17, Folder 6)
      3 items: cover letter dated October 23, 1933 from Frank Mittauer with 22 pages of questions for radio program; 2 copies of 11 p ms in response to questions about developments in Nazi Germany.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Cover letter; Reviews of Feuchtwanger and Doblin's books]. typewrittem ms; 7 p. (Box 17, Folder 7)
      2 items: cover letter to unidentified source regarding book reviews by Leonard; book review in German by Leonard with handwritten corrections.
    - Leonard, Alfred. Selbstmord. Grunde unbekannt. typewritten ms; 6 p. (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Text in German.
    - Leonard, Alfred. Honeymoon Island or Bandits Incorporated. xerox; 3 p. (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Story contains stamp from Screen Writer's Guild of the Author's League of America and xerox of check to Alfred Leonard from Screen Writer's Guild for $1 dated August 2, 1937,
  - By Joseph Leonard, Subseries 2.
    - Leonard, Joseph. [Writings on Beethoven and musical analysis]. typewritten ms; 31 p. (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Papers written in German while in Mannheim in 3 parts: Analysis of Beethoven's Sonata op. 10, no. 1 September 5, 1927 (6 pp.); biography of Beethoven August 1927 (11 pp.); "Die Dreiklange" August 1927 (15 pp.).
  - By Ernst Toch, Subseries 3.
    - Toch, Ernst. Amor Artis Bulletin; "The Cantata of the Bitter Herbs". magazine; 10 p. (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Amor Artis Bulletin volume 2 no. 1, December 1962. Contains Toch's article on The Cantata of the Bitter Herbs with English translation of the text, and review of Cantata by Frederick Freedman.
    - Toch, Ernst. Die dreiziffrige Zahl. typewritten ms; 3 p. (Box 17, Folder 15)
      Presumably by Toch; original location with other materials by Toch. Paper in German.
    - [Unidentified author]. [Biography of Ernst Toch on the occassion of his 75th birthday]. ozalid; 2 p. (Box 17, Folder 16)
      In German.
    - Toch, Ernst. Some Viewpoints of the Composer. offprint; 6 p. (Box 17, Folder 17)
      2 copies. Lecture given May 23, 1957 during 3rd Composer's Workshops, sponsored by the Westside Jewish Community Center.
    - Strecker. Ernst Toch Biography - Translation from German. ozalid; 2 p. (Box 17, Folder 18)
      Translation from German of speech given in honor of Toch's 75th birthday.
    - Toch, Ernst. Symphony no. 2, Op. 73. xerox; 1 p. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      P.15 from unidentified source. Notes on compositional process for Symphony no. 2.
  - By Stephen Flichtman, Subseries 4.
    - Flichtman, Stephen. The East Wind Prevails over the West Wind - China Report. offprint; 14 p. (Box 17, Folder 19)
      China report from September - October 1973, dated November 9, 1973.
    - Flichtman, Stephen. What is Your Agenda for 1974? 3 leaves. (Box 17, Folder 20)
      From sermon by Frichtman for the Unitarian church given December 30, 1973 at the First Unitarian Church of Los Angeles.
  - By Others, Subseries 5.
    - Sonderling, Jacob. Psalm 114. onionskin; 1 leaf. (Box 17, Folder 21)
      Interpretation by Sonderling.
    - Maltz, Albert. [Tribute to Stephen Frichtman]. xerox; 5 p. (Box 17, Folder 22)
      Xerox includes cover memo from Maltz to Alfred Leonard.
    - The Future of Man - Rosh Hashanah sermon. xerox; 6 p. (Box 17, Folder 23)
      Sermon given on first day of Rosh Hashanah in the year 5722.
    - Gruenewald, Max. Leo Baeck: Witness and Judge. offprint; 7 p. (Box 17, Folder 24)
      Offprint from Judaism- A Quarterly Journal of Jewish Life and Thought vol. 6 no. 3, summer 1957.
    - [Fragment of musical analysis paper]. onionskin; 1 p. (Box 17, Folder 25)
      Musical analysis of four movements of unidentified string quartet.
    - Lieberson, Goddard. Victor Babin - Obituary. 1 leaf. (Box 18, Folder 17)
      5 copies of obituary delivered at Fairmont Temple, Cleaveland Ohio Memorial Service, March 3, 1972.
    - [Unidentified notes and prescription]. 3 p. (Box 20, Folder 11)
      3 items: note with [monetary?] sums in pencil; note from Marjorie R. Leonard with bibliographic citation for Henry Bett's Nursery Rhymes and Tales; physician's prescription for Marjorie Leonard dated February 19, 1951.
    - [List of names and organizations]. handwritten ms; 1 leaf. (Box 21, Folder 23)
      Note possibly related to Joseph Levi immigration materials.
    - [New Year's greetings pamphlet from Rolf and Gusta Hoffman]. 1 leaf. (Box 21, Folder 38)
      Pamphlet folds out to poster; contains information on Goethe, dated 1934.
- Scrap Books, Series VIII.
  - P. Alfred Leonard, Subseries 1.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Music Guild Scrapbook]. 96 p. (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Contains newspaper clippings on Music Guild sponsored concerts and events 1945-1947.
    - Leonard, P. Alfred. [Scrapbook 1935-1936]. 72 p. (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Contains newspaper clippings, correspondence regarding activities of Alfred Leonard and radio programs on KFAC from 1935-1936.
  - Joseph Leonard, Subseries 2.
    - Leonard, Joseph. [Scrapbook]. 47 p. (Box 9, Folder 47)
      Contains photos and clippings from 1923-1936 regarding performances of Joseph Leonard in Germany.
- Music Programs, Series IX.
  - Pertaining to P. Alfred Leonard, Subseries 1.
    - [Music Guild Program First Season 1945-1946]. brochure; 12 p. (Box 17, Folder 34)
      Program includes notes written by Alfred Leonard with background information on pieces to be performed. Original location of program in front of Alfred Leonard's Music Guild scrapbook. See box 7/9.
    - [Music Guild presentation of Geza Anda, pianist]. 8 p. (Box 20, Folder 31)
      Concert held Wednesday, November 28, 1956 at Wilshire Ebell Theatre.
    - [Music Guild Seventh Annual 1951-1952 Concert Series]. 4 p. (Box 20, Folder 32)
      3 copies; contains 1951-1952 concert programs, list of 1952-1953 artists, list of board of trustees.
    - Music Guild Program 1951-1952 Season. 8 p. (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Program for seventh annual season.
    - The Los Angeles Music Guild Program 1956. 4 p. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Program for eleventh season.
  - Pertaining to Joseph Leonard, Subseries 2.
    - [Sunday Bohemians Program]. leaflet; 2 p. (Box 17, Folder 26)
      Program to Sunday Bohemians concert with Manuel Compinsky, director at the Pacific Institute of Music and Fine Art Monday June 7. Joseph Leonard performed Eroica Variations and Finale alla Fuga in Eb by Beethoven. Original location inserted into leaves of Joseph Leonard scrapbook. See 9/47.
    - Post-Shavouth Concert program - Westwood Temple. program; 4 p. (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Concert of The Guild of Temple Organists of Southen California, May 27, 1953 at Westwood Temple, with Joseph Leonard, organist. Original location in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook, clipped to Joseph Leonard material. See 8/5.
    - [Program for Genevieve Wiley and Joseph L. Leonard joint recital]. 1 leaf. (Box 18, Folder 10)
      2 copies of program for concert sponsored by the Lions Club of Fullerton at Fullerton Union High School, November 5, 1941. Back of page contains biography of Joseph Leonard. Original location in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook, clipped to Joseph Leonard material. See 8/5.
    - [Program for Joseph Leonard piano recital]. 1 leaf. (Box 18, Folder 12)
      3 copies of program for recital sponsored by Pacific Institute of Music and Fine Art at 3189 Wilshire Blvd on October 16, 1936. Original location of 1 copy in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook. See 8/5.
    - [Program for "In a Composer's Workshop" with Joseph Leonard, pianist-lecturer]. 1 leaf. (Box 18, Folder 13)
      Program of 6 workshops sponsored by Pacific Institute of Music and Fine Art at 3189 Wilshire Blvd, January 14 - March 25, 1937. Original location in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook. See 8/5.
    - [Concert of Jewish music from the 16th century]. 4 p; xerox copy. (Box 20, Folder 10)
      2 items, original program and xerox copy of concert held at Temple Beth Am, Friday, March 5, 1963, entitled "A Sixteenth Century Service celebrating Jewish Music Month". Joseph Leonard served as organist and choir director.
    - [Concerts held in Mannheim]. 5 programs; 6 leaves. (Box 20, Folder 17)
      5 items: concert held Tuesday, October 21, 1924 in Mannheim(?); performance of Joseph Levi [Leonard]'s Intrada and Ernst Toch's Adagio among other works February 16, 1930 sponsored by Judisches Lehrhaus Mannheim; Festkonzet and Festak celebrating 75th jubilee held January 17, 1931 Musensalle des Stadt; concert held December 27, 1932 sponsored by C. V. Jungend as part of Chanuka fair in which Joseph Levi [Leonard] performed Moaus Zur on organ; concert held at Hauptsynagoge November 3, 1935 in Mannheim in which Joseph Levi [Leonard] sang baritone.
    - [Concerts at Temple Beth Am]. programs; 4 leaves. (Box 20, Folder 18)
      3 items: "A Concert of Jewish Music" with Joseph Leonard, organist featuring premiere of Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco's Silent Devotion (n.d.); "Sing Unto the Lord" Friday, June 5, 1959 with Joseph Leonard, organist; "Hassidic Service in Celebration of Jewish Music Month" held Friday February 16, 1962 with Joseph Leonard organist and choir director.
    - [Concerts at Olympic Jewish Temple]. programs; 2 leaves. (Box 20, Folder 19)
      2 items: concert "Sabbath Evening in Vienna" held January 27, 1956 with Joseph Leonard, organist and choir director; concert "Sabbath Evening in Los Angeles" held February 24, 1956 with Joseph Leonard, organist and choir director.
    - [Guild of Temple Organists Concert]. 1 leaf. (Box 20, Folder 20)
      First Annual concert for Jewish Music Month held February 25, 1953 at Hollywood Temple Beth-El featuring compositions of Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco and as guest of honor. Joseph Leonard, organist.
    - Sacred Chants of Church and Synagogue. program; 1 leaf. (Box 20, Folder 21)
      Concert held at Leo Baeck Temple, sponsored by Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion on Wednesday, October 23, 1963. Includes performance of Joseph Leonard's composition, Ashre Yoshve Vesecho.
    - [Joseph Leonard, piano soloist with Inglewood Symphony Orchestra]. program; 10 p. (Box 20, Folder 22)
      Concert held at George Green auditorium May 24, 1953, sponsored by Centinela Music Association.
    - [10th Anniversary Tribute to Joseph Leonard, organist]. program; 4 p; telegrams; 10 p. (Box 20, Folder 26)
      2 items: program; 10 telegrams sending best wishes to Joseph Leonard. Program held Monday, December 9, 1963 as part of Temple Beth Am semi annual general membership meeting.
  - Other, Subseries 3.
    - [Grauden Ensemble]. 4 p. (Box 20, Folder 13)
      Concert presented by the Community Concert Association, affiliated with Columbia Artists Management Inc. Appears to be from 1958-1959 concert season. No specific date or location given.
    - [Mock concert program]. mimeograph; 1 p. (Box 20, Folder 14)
      Title "Leider-Abend" with modified composer's names and comic song titles.
    - [Musical reception in honor of Ernst Toch's 75th Birthday]. 1 p. (Box 20, Folder 27)
      Program included peformance of works by Ernst Toch: Dedication 1957; Capriccettii op. 36; Burlesques op. 31; String Quartet no. 13 op. 74. Speeches by Dr. Wilhelm Schlag, Peter Jona Korn, Alfred Leonard. Date and location not indicated on program.
    - William Tell. 16 p. (Box 20, Folder 35)
      Music composed by Ernst Toch. No date or location for performance given.
    - Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra 29th Season 1947-1948. 44 p. (Box 20, Folder 36)
      Program stored open to p. 457 for Schnabel concert.
    - Vitya Vronsky and Victor Babin in a program for two pianos. 4 p. (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Concert held during 1959-1960 season, sponsored by The Community Concert Association.
- Documents, Series X.
  - Legal contracts and documents, Subseries 1.
    - Amtsblatt des badischen ministeriums des kultus und unterrichts. 6 p. (Box 18, Folder 9)
      German language document dated May 22, 1928 regarding regulations for music instruction. Pp. 121-126. Original location in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook, clipped to Joseph Leonard material. See 8/5.
    - [Documents of legal partnership between Leonards and Jake Zeitlin]. 13 p. (Box 21, Folder 36)
      3 items: signed mimeograph letter to Jake Zeitlin terminating employment dated July 10, 1935; signed agreement dissolving partnership between Marjorie Leonard and Jake Zeitlin dated July 13, 1935; agreement of limited partnership between Jake Zeitlin and Marjorie Leonard signed March 31, 1935.
  - Certificates of birth, citizenship etc., Subseries 2.
    - [Certificate of completion for Joseph Levi [Leonard] from Mannheim Music School]. (Box 17, Folder 27)
      2 items: document from Mannheim Hochschule fur Musik in Mannheim dated March 27, 1928; envelope with Bernhard Levi return address. Original location inserted in Joseph Leonard's scrapbook. See 9/47.
    - Certificate Joseph Levi [Leonard] completion of music instruction. onionskin; 1 p. (Box 20, Folder 30)
      Document in German dated October 25, 1927 from Mannheim music school.
    - Reife-Zeugnis fur Joseph Levi [Leonard]. certificate; 4 p; 2 photographs 5.5x3.5; certificate folder. (Box 21, Folder 8)
      3 items: German language document dated October 24-25, 1927 certifiying completion of piano program from Music program in Mannheim; 2 photographs of document; certificate folder.
    - [Certificate for Joseph Levi from Ministry of Culture; private instruction]. certificate; 2 photographs 5.5x3.5. (Box 21, Folder 9)
      2 items: certificate dated April 23, 1930; 2 photographs of certificate.
    - [Joseph Levi certificate from Stern'schen Konservatoriums, Berlin]. 4 p. (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Document dated September 1, 1923.
    - [Joseph Levi certificates from Mannheim Hochschule fur Musik]. 2 p. (Box 21, Folder 12)
      2 items: certificate dated March 18, 1930; dated March 19, 1930.
    - Reichstartell der deutschen Musiterschaft e. S. fragebogen [Joseph Levi]. document; 3 leaves. (Box 21, Folder 16)
      3 copies of document dated and signed in Mannheim, February 2, 1934.
    - [Document concerning Moritz Meyer Kaufmann and Bernhard Levi Kaufmann]. 8 p. (Box 21, Folder 17)
      Document dated 1912.
    - Ausfietigung. back cover; 12 p. (Box 21, Folder 18)
      2 items: green cover; document dated July 16, 1902.
    - Staatsangerhorigseitsausweis [Joseph Levi]. 1 p. (Box 21, Folder 19)
      Document dated March 17, 1930.
    - Fuhrungzengnis [Joseph Levi]. 1 p. (Box 21, Folder 21)
      Document dated and signed in Berlin, November 3, 1927.
    - Selfhelp of German Emigrees. [Document for Joseph Levi]. 3 leaves. (Box 21, Folder 22)
      Document in German dated December 1936.
    - [Document for piano private instruction for Joseph Levi [Leonard]]. mimeograph onionskin; 1 leaf. (Box 21, Folder 24)
      Document from Ministerium des Kulturs und Unterrichts, dated April 23, 1930.
    - Geburtsurkunde. 1 leaf. (Box 21, Folder 25)
      Document dated February 10, 1937.
    - Geburt urtunde. 1 leaf. (Box 21, Folder 26)
      Document dated Februrary 10, 1937.
    - Leumunds-Zeugnis [for Josef Levi [Joseph Leonard]]. photostat; 1 p. (Box 21, Folder 28)
      Document dated February 17, 1937.
    - Leumunds-Zeugnis [for Bernhard Levi]. photostat; 1 p. (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - [Envelope from U.S. Department of Labor]. envelope. (Box 21, Folder 30)
      Envelope dated June 2?, 1937. Contents missing.
    - [Telegrams]. 4 leaves. (Box 21, Folder 31)
      4 telegrams: dated May 10-11, 1933 from Jim regarding checks; dated October 19, 1933 from Howard regarding visa extension; dated October 18, 1933 from Howard to Alfred regarding Washington taking care of forgotten men; dated May 8, 1937 from Josephthal to Leonard regarding student work.
    - [Letter of recommendation for Joseph Levi [Leonard]]. handwritten ms; 1 leaf. (Box 21, Folder 33)
      Letter dated February 10 from Dr. Emil Wertheimer.
    - [Immigration card for Joseph Levi]. card. (Box 21, Folder 34)
      Card dated December 18, 1937.
    - Certificate of Naturalization for Joseph Leonard. 1 p. (Box 21, Folder 35)
      Document dated November 12, 1943.
  - Other Financial Documents, Subseries 3.
    - [Material regarding possessions of Peg Batelle]. 4 leaves. (Box 21, Folder 40)
      3 items, all located in folder "Peg Batelle (Alfred Leonard's mother in law)": handwritten letter to Alfred Leonard dated September 24, 1937; 2 page typewritten list of items and monetary value; typewritten poem by Gene Fowler, "A Blue Book Tragedy".
- Catalogues and Brochures, Series XI.
  - Leonard, Alfred, ed. [Catalogue for The Music Shop, Hollywood - Gateway to Music]. 9 p. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Catalogue dated February 1937, volume 1 number 1; lists records with prices, label and review of each recording for sale at the Music Shop. Original location in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook. See 8/5.
  - [Brochure for Pacific Institute of Music and Fine Art]. 4 p. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Original location in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook. See 8/5.
  - Dedication - Wall of the Martyred Six Million April 24, 1966. 14 p. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Booklet prepared by Temple Beth Am. Original location in front of Alfred Leonard scrapbook. See 8/5.
  - Columbia Artists Management. Vronsky and Babin Twenty-Fifth Anniversary. 8 p. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Press release in brochure format of Vronsky-Babin duo with photographs and discography promoting and soliciting 1961-1962 bookings.
  - Berkshire Music Center. brochure; 16 p; application; 4 p. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    2 items: brochure marking 25th anniversary in 1965; application for admission for June 27 - August 22, 1965.
  - Pacific Instistute of Music and Fine Art Magazine and Catalogue. 34 p; 1 leaf. (Box 20, Folder 23)
    3 items: 2 copies of March issue of catalogue (1936?) one with pp.27-28 missing; torn out pp. 27-28, possibly for use in scrapbook.
  - Ernst Toch Catalogue of Works. 24 p. (Box 20, Folder 28)
    2 copies of catalogue published by Associated Music Publishers Inc. New York including a short biography.
  - Partial list of works by Ernst Toch. typewritten ms; 3 p. (Box 20, Folder 29)
    Works listed according to performances by prominent conductors and soloists. Some data filled in with pencil.
  - [Pacific Institute brochure, flyers, programs]. 40 p. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    6 items: March (1936?) issue of Pacific Institute of Music and Fine Art brochure; flyer for L. May, instructor in professional and commercial art; flyer for Compinsky Trio; program for Compinsky Trio concert Monday, November 8; application for Compinsky music system enrollment; flyer for Jacobina Caro, modern dance instructor. All flyers and program were inserted in brochure. See also 20/23 for other copies of brochure.
  - [Catalogue of Ernst Toch works]. 1 leaf. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Catalogue published by Associated Music Publishers, Inc.
  - Ernst Toch at UCLA. flyer; 2 p. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    List of recent Toch publications at UCLA Ernst Toch Archives.